http://www.fibrex.co.uk/pages/privacy-policy

Login /
Sign-Up /
Wishlist
Home of the National Collection of Pelargonium & the National Collection of Hedera
0
items
£0.00
View Order
Your shopping cart is empty!
Helix
Helix ssp.
Asplenium
Athyrium (british)
Cystopteris
Dryopteris (british)
Fern Collection
Gymnocarpium
Osmunda
Polypodium (british)
Polystichum (british)
Thelypteris (british)
Adiantum
Athyrium (foreign)
Coniogramme
Cyrtomium
Dryopteris (foreign)
Matteuccia
Onoclea
Polypodium (foreign)
Polystichum (foreign)
Rumora
Thelypteris (foreign)
Contact
Home of the National Collection of Pelargonium & the National Collection of Hedera
£0.00 View Order
Your shopping cart is empty!
Helix
Helix ssp.
Asplenium
Athyrium (british)
Cystopteris
Dryopteris (british)
Fern Collection
Gymnocarpium
Osmunda
Polypodium (british)
Polystichum (british)
Thelypteris (british)
Hardy Foreign Ferns
Adiantum
Athyrium (foreign)
Coniogramme
Cyrtomium
Dryopteris (foreign)
Matteuccia
Onoclea
Polypodium (foreign)
Polystichum (foreign)
Rumhora
Thelypteris (foreign)
Woodwardia
Shipping week of 22nd March 2021
Begonia corms are dispatched from mid February until late March. These are started into growth (not dormant). Corms should therefore be potted as soon as you receive them according to the cultural information you will receive with your corms.
Keep at a temperature of around 16°C. Keep compost moist, pot on as necessary, preferably with a soil based compost, e.g. John Innes No. 2. Removal of the first flower buds when the plant is small will mean larger flowers later on.
Shipping week of 22nd February 2021
Tropical Hibiscus are native to China but are widely grown throughout the tropics & sub-tropics where they can reach up to 2m. They are tender in Britain and grown as
house/conservatory plants where they can be kept in check with pruning and if grown in good, natural daylight have large, showy flowers through summer & autumn.
Shipping week of 12TH APRIL 2021
Our range of Conservatory plants give a cross section of colour and scents for year round interest. Most tender shrubs and climbers can be grown in containers of varying sizes and types outside for the summer months and then transferred back into the conservatory for the winter.
In some cases however, tender plants are kept in the conservatory and wall trained or grown to provide a canopy to shade other plants and to create an environment that is comfortable to live with.
Shipping week of 12TH APRIL 2021
These easy to grow perennials come in an assortment of colours and are suitable for both dry shade or full sun. Exceptionally hardy, they are ideal cottage garden plants
for mixed borders and can make great companions for ferns in shady spots, giving colour where it is much needed.
Shipping week of 22nd March 2021
Coming Soon
Shipping week of 22nd March 2021
About us
News
Contact
Home of the National Collection of Pelargonium & the National Collection of Hedera
Privacy Policy
Home
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Fibrex Nurseries Ltd Privacy PolicyThis Privacy Policy describes how your personal information is collected, used, and shared when you visit or make a purchase from www.fibrex.co.uk (the “Site”).PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECTWhen you visit the Site, we automatically collect certain information about your device, including information about your web browser, IP address, time zone, and some of the cookies that are installed on your device. Additionally, as you browse the Site, we collect information about the individual web pages or products that you view, what websites or search terms referred you to the Site, and information about how you interact with the Site. We refer to this automatically-collected information as “Device Information.”We collect Device Information using the following technologies: - “Cookies” are data files that are placed on your device or computer and often include an anonymous unique identifier. For more information about cookies, and how to disable cookies, visit http://www.allaboutcookies.org. - “Log files” track actions occurring on the Site, and collect data including your IP address, browser type, Internet service provider, referring/exit pages, and date/time stamps. - “Web beacons,” “tags,” and “pixels” are electronic files used to record information about how you browse the Site. Additionally when you make a purchase or attempt to make a purchase through the Site, we collect certain information from you, including your name, billing address, shipping address, payment information (including credit card numbers, debit card numbers and paypal), email address, and phone number. We refer to this information as “Order Information.”When we talk about “Personal Information” in this Privacy Policy, we are talking both about Device Information and Order Information.HOW DO WE USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?We use the Order Information that we collect generally to fulfill any orders placed through the Site (including processing your payment information, arranging for shipping, and providing you with invoices and/or order confirmations). Additionally, we use this Order Information to:Communicate with you;Screen our orders for potential risk or fraud; andWhen in line with the preferences you have shared with us, provide you with information or advertising relating to our products or services.We use the Device Information that we collect to help us screen for potential risk and fraud (in particular, your IP address), and more generally to improve and optimize our Site (for example, by generating analytics about how our customers browse and interact with the Site, and to assess the success of our marketing and advertising campaigns).SHARING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATIONWe share your Personal Information with third parties to help us use your Personal Information, as described above. For example, we use Shopify to power our online store--you can read more about how Shopify uses your Personal Information here: https://www.shopify.com/legal/privacy. We also use Google Analytics to help us understand how our customers use the Site--you can read more about how Google uses your Personal Information here: https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/. You can also opt-out of Google Analytics here: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.Finally, we may also share your Personal Information to comply with applicable laws and regulations, to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other lawful request for information we receive, or to otherwise protect our rights.Additionally, you can opt out of some of these services by visiting the Digital Advertising Alliance’s opt-out portal at: http://optout.aboutads.info/.DO NOT TRACKPlease note that we do not alter our Site’s data collection and use practices when we see a Do Not Track signal from your browser.YOUR RIGHTSIf you are a European resident, you have the right to access personal information we hold about you and to ask that your personal information be corrected, updated, or deleted. If you would like to exercise this right, please contact us through the contact information below.Additionally, if you are a European resident we note that we are processing your information in order to fulfill contracts we might have with you (for example if you make an order through the Site), or otherwise to pursue our legitimate business interests listed above. Additionally, please note that your information will be transferred outside of Europe, including to Canada and the United States.DATA RETENTIONWhen you place an order through the Site, we will maintain your Order Information for our records unless and until you ask us to delete this information.CHANGESWe may update this privacy policy from time to time in order to reflect, for example, changes to our practices or for other operational, legal or regulatory reasons.CONTACT USFor more information about our privacy practices, if you have questions, or if you would like to make a complaint, please contact us by e-mail at sales@fibrex.co.uk or by mail using the details provided below: Honeybourne Road, Pebworth, Warks, CV378XP, United Kingdom
